http://www.hugeweddingsavings.com/pages/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address, phone number, email address to fulfil your order request, including a final verification email that you have received your merchandise in good order.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address to determine the country you are browsing from, so we can provide prices in the correct currency.You will never receive promotional literature, unless you explicitly opt-in for our Newsletter.SECTION 2 - CONSENTHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.We will never use your personal information for a secondary reason unless you give us explicit consent.  If you give us this consent, we would only use your personal information for the exact purpose that you gave us approval for.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at crm@httpwebsales.com SECTION 3 - DISCLOSUREWe will only disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do.SECTION 4 - PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and PAYMENT SECURITY
This website provides end-to-end 256-bit encryption technology providing the same level of encryption used by large banks to keep your information secure.  This website encrypts all browsing and transactional activities including personally identifiable and payment information from the moment you enter our site, up to and including the point you leave our site.
Also, our hosting platform is certified Level 1 PCI DSS Compliant, the highest level of security, which encompasses the following best practices, procedures and policies:
Maintain a Secure Network
Protect Cardholder Data
Maintain a Vulnerability Management Program
Implement Strong Access Control Measures
Regularly Monitor and Test Networks
Maintain an Information Security Policy
We NEVER store your credit card data on our servers. Your payment information is processed in real-time over a secure encrypted channel directly with the issuing bank.
SECTION 5 - COOKIESSome cookies are necessary to allow you to browse our website, use its features, and access secure areas. The use of these cookies is essential for the website to work. The cookies contain no personally identifiable information about you. We also use cookies to assist with anonymous aggregate statistical information such as site traffic analysis, which includes tracking the time/date of visits, pages viewed, and referring URLs.SECTION 6 - AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.SECTION 7 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, please contact us at crm@httpwebsales.com.
